<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<content id="ws_2463118472" name="Reaction Force" author="Shibdib" version="211" date="2025-05-18" save="0" description="So because steam is annoying I had to push the update back on the OG link as it won't let me update this one despite being listed as a contributor. Please unsub here and resub at the link. All the thanks to I.C.E. for keeping this thing going in my absence. &#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2069655173&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;- Shibdib&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;[i]Originally created by Shibdib: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2069655173&#13;&#10;This is an enhanced version of the original script, published with Shibdib's permission.[/i]&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;[b]Can be installed and uninstalled without starting a new game. Existing order upon mod removal will reset to 'Hold position'[/b]&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;[b]What it does?[/b]&#13;&#10;It adds a new default command for playr ships, that will automatically respond to ships in distress.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;[b]What's the difference between this and original[/b]&#13;&#10;- You can select what ships do when they are not responding. There are a few options.&#13;&#10;- Before responding, your AI captains will evaluate the expected threat and may not respond if the fight is a predicted loss. You can choose the threshold.&#13;&#10;- This script controls subordinates diffrently. Not all of the subordinates will become a reaction force of their own. Details in instructions.&#13;&#10;- Captains do send &quot;resupply&quot; signal to their subordinates.&#13;&#10;- Plus a few more options to give you more control over what your captains can and can't do.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;[b]How to use it?[/b]&#13;&#10;Instructions are here: https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/discussion/2463118472/4679778856510205486/&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;[b]Known bugs / limitations[/b]&#13;&#10;- Reaction to Ally distress signals is NOT properly tested. It was updated to match the response script, that is used to help player ships in distress, but might not work properly.&#13;&#10;- RF captains may sometimes chase enemy ships far away from their AoO. The reason behind this is how vanilla attack mechanics is working. Not yet sure about a solution. It only happens if the fight does NOT begin before the enemy starts running away. For example: When a pirate attacks and kills your trader and leaves the place before RF have a chance to arrive. They will chase this pirate until they catch 'im.&#13;&#10;- Response might not be sent to Large (and maybe X-Large) ships, if the damage taken is neglegible. The reason for this is currently unknown.&#13;&#10;- I would expect an incompatibility if you have this and the original script active at the same time&#13;&#10;- Subordinates set to Defend the commander [i]may[/i] glitch. Not that I've ever seen it, but I haven't properly test them yet." lastupdate="1682438443">
  <text language="44" name="Reaction Force" author="Shibdib" description="Adds a multi sector reaction force command."></text>
  <text language="49" name="Reaktions streitkräfte" author="Shibdib" description="Fügt einen Befehl zur Reaktion auf mehrere Sektoren hinzu."></text>
  <text language="81" name="即応部隊" author="Shibdib" description="多部門即応部隊司令部を追加する"></text>
  <text language="86" name="反应部队" author="Shibdib" description="增加多部门反应部队指挥部"></text>
</content>